[Music]
This is the first time that I
am at home for so many days I have been working for 20 years and have bought
this house Time has flown so fast
My little kids are now teenagers I was about to get a
big promotion on the career front,
but now I am just thankful to have
stability in my job In today's uncertainty,
I am looking for a plan that will
protect my family's future My family should never be worried about our
home loan, no matter what
And the children should never have to compromise whether it is studies or career Joy
I just want the
best for my kids Now it has become
very important to plan for health expenses as well
[Music]